<resources>
    <string name="app_name">MoBetes </string>

    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->

    <string-array name="condition">
        <item>Fasting</item>
        <item>2 hour after meal</item>
        <item>Before meal</item>

        <!--<item>HbA1c</item>-->
        <!--<item>Random</item>-->
    </string-array>


    <string-array name="meal">
        <item>Breakfast</item>
        <item>Lunch</item>
        <item>Dinner</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="mood">
        <item>Happy</item>
        <item>Good</item>
        <item>Cheerful</item>
        <item>Bad</item>
        <item>Sad</item>
        <item>Stressed</item>
    </string-array>

    <string name="open">Open</string>
    <string name="close">Close</string>
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="accept">Accept</string>
    <string name="eula_string">

End-User License Agreement (EULA) of MoBetes

\n\nThis End-User License Agreement (EULA) is a legal agreement between you and MDH

\n\nThis EULA agreement governs your acquisition and use of our MoBetes application ("application") directly from MDH or indirectly through a MDH authorized reseller or distributor.

\n\nPlease read this EULA agreement carefully before completing the installation process and using the MoBetes application. It provides a license to use the MoBetes application and contains warranty information and liability disclaimers.

\n\nIf you register for a free trial of the MoBetes application, this EULA agreement will also govern that trial. By clicking "accept" or installing and/or using the MoBetes application, you are confirming your acceptance of the application and agreeing to become bound by the terms of this EULA agreement.

\n\nIf you are entering into this EULA agreement on behalf of a company or other legal entity, you represent that you have the authority to bind such entity and its affiliates to these terms and conditions. If you do not have such authority or if you do not agree with the terms and conditions of this EULA agreement, do not install or use the application, and you must not accept this EULA agreement.

\n\nThis EULA agreement shall apply only to the application supplied by MDH herewith regardless of whether other application is referred to or described herein. The terms also apply to any MDH updates, supplements, Internet-based services, and support services for the application, unless other terms accompany those items on delivery. If so, those terms apply.

\n\n\nLicense Grant
\n\nMDH hereby grants you a personal, non-transferable, non-exclusive licence to use the MoBetes application on your devices in accordance with the terms of this EULA agreement.

\n\nYou are permitted to load the MoBetes application (for example a PC, laptop, mobile or tablet) under your control. You are responsible for ensuring your device meets the minimum requirements of the MoBetes application.

\n\nYou are not permitted to:

\n\nEdit, alter, modify, adapt, translate or otherwise change the whole or any part of the application nor permit the whole or any part of the application to be combined with or become incorporated in any other application, nor decompile, disassemble or reverse engineer the application or attempt to do any such things
\n\nReproduce, copy, distribute, resell or otherwise use the application for any commercial purpose
\n\nAllow any third party to use the application on behalf of or for the benefit of any third party
\n\nUse the application in any way which breaches any applicable local, national or international law
\n\nuse the application for any purpose that MDH considers is a breach of this EULA agreement
\n\n\nIntellectual Property and Ownership
\n\nMDH shall at all times retain ownership of the application as originally downloaded by you and all subsequent downloads of the application by you. The application (and the copyright, and other intellectual property rights of whatever nature in the application, including any modifications made thereto) are and shall remain the property of MDH.

\n\nMDH reserves the right to grant licences to use the application to third parties.

\n\n\nTermination
\n\nThis EULA agreement is effective from the date you first use the application and shall continue until terminated. You may terminate it at any time upon written notice to MDH.

\n\nIt will also terminate immediately if you fail to comply with any term of this EULA agreement. Upon such termination, the licenses granted by this EULA agreement will immediately terminate and you agree to stop all access and use of the application. The provisions that by their nature continue and survive will survive any termination of this EULA agreement.

\n\n\nGoverning Law
\n\nThis EULA agreement, and any dispute arising out of or in connection with this EULA agreement, shall be governed by and construed in accordance with the laws of Malaysia.</string>
</resources>
